Guide to the Hazel Reed papers, 1949-1954.
Reed, Hazel papers, 1949-1954
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Hazel Reed papers, 1949-1954.
23-17-270
Hazel. Reed
.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, newspaper articles/clippings, program documents, photos, pamphlets, meeting minutes, reports, & speeches.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Pamphlets, mimeographed circulars, a letter, and other items pertaining to public health and safety; also, newspaper clippings, letters, and circulars concerning the Home Bureau's sponsorship of a United Nations flag sewing project in 1950.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor emeritus of extension, College of Home Economics, Cornell University.
Hazel E. Reed received her B.A. from Cornell and her master's degree from Michigan State. She joined the College of Home Economics faculty in 1949 as associate professor in cooperative extension work. She became an associate state leader in 1954, a professor in extension in 1962, a state leader in 1965, and assistant director in 1966. She retired as assistant director of extension and full professor in 1967.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Pamphlets, mimeographed circulars, a letter, and other items pertaining to public health and safety; also, newspaper clippings, letters, and circulars concerning the Home Bureau's sponsorship of a United Nations flag sewing project in 1950.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Reed, Hazel.; New York State College of Home Economics--Faculty.; United Nations.
Subjects:
Flags.; Home economics extension work.; Public health.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Health & Safety College Committee & Personnel, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- U.N. Flag News Articles, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- U.N. Flag News Articles, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Health & Safety Objectives of H&S Program, New York State Extension, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Health & Safety Committee County Extension- 4H, HB, FB, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Health & Safety Committee Reports & Speeches, 1951-1952 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Health & Safety- New York State Extension Service Coordinating Committee Personnel & Minutes, 1950, 52, 53 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Health & Safety Correspondence to Health Specialists from USDA, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Health & Safety Committee Correspondence- general, 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Health & Safety College Committee Minutes & Personnel, 1951-1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Health & Safety Committee Activities, 1952-1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Program for Health & Safety Committee- New York State Federation of Home Bureaus, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Health & Safety- Rural Health Conference, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)